<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic xml:lang="en-US" id="c-standard-library-v2-migration-guide_2">
    <title>Features Not Supported in the XXX Library</title>
    <shortdesc>Short description.</shortdesc>
    <body>
        <section id="section_s12_gl3_ddc"><title> Section title </title>Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. Placeholder text. </section>
    </body>
</topic>
